<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>Urmoit Studio</author>
    <version>1.0.2.0</version>
    <iconFilename>MainIcon.dds</iconFilename>

    <title>
        <en>Better Capacity for Vehicles</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[The capacity is being adjusted based on what the community wants, ensuring it meets player expectations.
More tractors, trailers, and vehicle capacities can be improved. Just let me know which vehicle’s capacity you’d like to see increased!
    
The capacity will be adjusted based on community feedback, ensuring it aligns with what players want once the mod is completed.
This mod for Farming Simulator 25 focuses on one simple but highly effective improvement: increasing the capacity of vehicles and trailers already in the game. By modifying existing assets, it ensures you can transport more with each load, saving you time and effort during your farming operations.

What the Mod Does:
1. Increased Capacity: Boosts the load capacity of combines, trailers, and other vehicles to hold more grain, silage, or other materials.
2. Efficiency Improvements: Reduces the frequency of unloading, allowing you to focus on farming tasks instead of constantly managing storage.
3. No New Models: This mod takes the original equipment from the game and adjusts its capacity, keeping the familiar look and feel of your favorite vehicles.

Why Use This Mod?
If you’re tired of frequent trips to unload your harvest or materials, "Better Capacity for Vehicles" provides a solution by maximizing the storage potential of existing machines in Farming Simulator 25.
Spend more time farming and less time unloading with this straightforward enhancement. Download the mod today and experience the convenience of better capacity!

ChangeLog
V1.0.1
    - Added Claas Evion 420 Compine Whit Bigger Capacity
    - Added SamsonAgro US 235 Dynamic Manure Trailer
V1.0.2
    - Added GRIMME Ventor 4150 potato harvestor
    - Added SALEK ANS-1900 Cheapest Trailer in the game
    - Removed SIDEKICK RTVXG 850
    - Made every vehicle prices lower
]]></en>
    </description>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/ventor4150.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/mf8570.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/evion450.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/us235.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/ans1900.xml"/>
    </storeItems>

</modDesc>
