<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="92">
    <author>Urmoit Studio</author>
    <version>1.0.3.0</version>
    <iconFilename>MainIcon.dds</iconFilename>

    <title>
        <en>Better Capacity for Vehicles</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Maximize your productivity with optimized capacities!
This mod is designed to improve Farming Simulator 25 gameplay by increasing the load capacities of existing vehicles and equipment. By making these tweaks, players can save time and focus on farming, reducing the hassle of frequent unloading trips.

Support me: https://paypal.me/urmoken

Features of the Mod
1. Enhanced Vehicle Capacities.
2. Combines, trailers, and other vehicles have received significant capacity boosts to carry more materials such as grain, silage, and potatoes.
Improved Efficiency.
3. Spend less time unloading and more time farming. With increased storage capabilities, you can focus on expanding your farm operations without interruptions.
4. Retained Original Design.
5. No new models are added. All changes are made to existing vehicles, preserving the game’s original look and feel while enhancing functionality.
Budget-Friendly Adjustments.
6. Lowered prices for all modified vehicles, ensuring upgrades are accessible even for players starting out.
Community-Centric Updates.
7. Vehicle and capacity improvements are continually refined based on feedback from the FS25 community. Let your voice be heard and shape the future of this mod!

What’s Included?
- Harvesters: All existing harvesters in FS25 now come with expanded capacity, reducing trips to unload during harvest seasons.
- Trailers: More trailers have been optimized, with expanded storage for various crops and materials.
- Special Equipment: Enhanced specific vehicles like potato harvesters for a smoother workflow.

Why You’ll Love It
- Tired of spending too much time unloading instead of enjoying the farming experience? The Better Capacity for Vehicles Mod brings a practical solution that fits seamlessly into FS25 gameplay. It’s simple, efficient, and guaranteed to improve your productivity. Whether you’re managing small fields or running a massive farm, this mod adapts to your needs.

Changelog
Version 1.0.2:
- Added GRIMME Ventor 4150 (Potato Harvester)
- Added SALEK ANS-1900 (Cheapest Trailer in the game)
- Removed SIDEKICK RTVXG 850
- Reduced prices for all vehicles

Version 1.0.3 (Biggest Update Yet):
- All combine harvesters now feature expanded capacities.
- Further updates and expansions are coming soon!
- Note: Unable to add the Fendt 5275 C SL, CLAAS LEXION 6900, NEW HOLLAND CR11 Gold Edition, and Case IH combines.

Ready to take your farming efficiency to the next level? Download the Better Capacity for Vehicles Mod today and experience the difference!
]]></en>
    </description>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/ventor4150.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/mf8570.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/evion450.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/us235.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/ans1900.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/beta7360AL4.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/axialFlow150.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/seriesS7.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/seriesX9.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/lexion8900.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/cr11.xml"/>
        
    </storeItems>

</modDesc>
